{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_6_DQJF5E",
                "player_7_DQJF5E",
                "player_11_DQJF5E",
                "player_9_DQJF5E",
                "player_12_DQJF5E"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                6,
                7,
                11,
                9,
                12
            ],
            "animation": [
                "liedown",
                "liedown",
                "stand",
                "crouch",
                "pick_up"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear.",
                "A bald man with glasses, dark complexion, wearing a black turtleneck, suit, and shoes",
                "A man with short black hair, wearing a white button-up shirt, dark pants, and black shoes. Light skin tone.",
                "A man with medium skin tone, wearing a navy blue polo shirt, black pants, and blue shoes, with a dark watch on his wrist and black hair.",
                "A man wearing a gray suit, dark shirt, and brown shoes with short dark hair."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -60579.666,
                    77818.648,
                    -5851.319,
                    0,
                    -157.48964671367602,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -60662.725,
                    77934.972,
                    -5818.201,
                    0,
                    -141.93683857934212,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -60964.829,
                    77440.707,
                    -5780.974,
                    0,
                    -47.526903216996914,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -61018.164,
                    77298.509,
                    -5806.426,
                    0,
                    63.894796929302714,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -60613.951,
                    77567.318,
                    -5858.479,
                    0.0,
                    -89.998,
                    0.0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -61232.391,
            77290.879,
            -5762.996
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1061.6395628277505
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            -60189.474,
            77352.755,
            -5976.416,
            0,
            155.84947725063535,
            0
        ],
        [
            -60495.297,
            77016.961,
            -5984.841,
            0,
            114.61576348045658,
            0
        ],
        [
            -61145.042,
            77782.293,
            -5701.78,
            0,
            -24.287041801894244,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, the_bald_man_in_glasses or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_grey_suit"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, the_man_in_white_shirt or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_white_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_white_shirt, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_white_shirt, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_bald_man_in_glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_grey_suit"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_man_in_white_shirt or the_bald_man_in_glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_white_shirt",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_white_shirt"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many people are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "five"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many individuals are in a crouch position?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many people are lying down on the ground?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many women are in the scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many men are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene are bald?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many individuals have a medium skin color?",
                "answer": "three"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. liedown",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "A. liedown"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. liedown",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "C. liedown"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. liedown",
                    "B. stand",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. jumping"
                ],
                "answer": "B. stand"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. walk",
                    "B. run",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. liedown"
                ],
                "answer": "C. crouch"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. lying down",
                    "B. holding something",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. waving"
                ],
                "answer": "B. holding something"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the man in white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. To the front of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the man in white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the front-left of",
                    "C. To the front-right of",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the man in white shirt relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-left of",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the man in white shirt relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. To the front-left of",
                    "D. To the back-left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in glasses relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. Behind"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-right of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the front-left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the front-left of"
            }
        }
    }
}